YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
时间轴： godwuwen  孤帆  字幕总监： YY
翻译： 糊笑笑  非燕  猫中之王 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
校对： 赛不愿让你一个人  呷赛猫 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第二十二集
2012年5月  马修和莉莉
In May of 2012, Marshall and Lily
在家举办新生儿送礼会
hosted a baby shower in the apartment.
他们所有朋友都来了
All their friends were there.
我也确保自己准时在...
So of course I made sure to show up exactly...
3小时之后出现
...three hours late.
-我来晚了吗  -有点
- Oh, no! Am I late? - Little bit.
对不起  我是想早点到的
Ah, I'm sorry, I would've gotten here earlier;
-只是...  -你不想碰见罗宾
- it's just, um... - You didn't want to see Robin.
我不想碰见罗宾
I didn't want to see Robin.
我知道这样很幼稚
I know, it's childish.
她现在不在吧
She's not here, is she?
其实...
Actually...
我来早了吗
Oh, no! Am I early?
有点
Little bit.
她送的是红色婴儿车
Whoa, she got you the red stroller?
看来我的车青出于"蓝"胜于"蓝"啊
Looks like I just blew her out of the water.
反正她在派对开始前就走了
Anyway, she left before the party started.
真是不好意思
Ah, I'm really sorry, I...
我只是觉得我和罗宾
I just think it's best if Robin and I
这阵子最好先不要见面
don't see each other for a while.
泰德  我无所谓
Ted, it's fine;
我在离异家庭中长大
I'm a child of divorce.
你们爱怎么吵就怎么吵
You guys keep fighting all you want,
只要贵重礼物不间断就好
as long as the expensive gifts keep coming.
送礼会怎么样
Uh, so how was the shower?
挺好的
It was good,
虽然巴尼的脱衣舞娘女友
although there was one weird moment
有一度害气氛变得很尴尬
with Barney's new stripper girlfriend.
一天50个
50 laps a day?
天啊  小姑娘  那可真是太多了
Oh, my goodness, young lady. That is a lot.
是吗
Oh, is it?
有很多吗  路易丝奶奶
Is it a lot, Grandma Lois?
没错  我女朋友靠脱衣服
Yes, my girlfriend gets naked
坐在男人腿上跳舞挣钱
and sits on guys' laps for money.
没错  有时候一天她能坐50个大腿
And, yes, sometimes it's as many as 50 laps in one day.
也许社会会觉得她的工作
And maybe society considers what she does
很"恶心"
to be "disgusting,"
很"淫荡"
or "sutty,"
跟"做鸡"没区别
or verging on "prostitution,"
或就是"做鸡"
or actual "prostitution."
但我接受她
But you know what, I accept her.
如果你不能接受她
And if you can't do the same,
那我真为你感到羞耻
well, then shame on you.
为你
Shame...
感到
on...
羞耻
you.
我们其实在说游泳
We were, um, talking about swimming.
说我一天能游50个来回
How I sometimes swim 50 laps a day.
挺好的有氧运动啊
Well, it's great cardio.
奶奶  我帮您加点香槟吧
Lois, can I top off your champagne?
说来也好笑
You know, it's funny,
你告诉普通男人  你和脱衣舞女约会
you tell the average guy you're dating a stripper,
他会觉得超级棒
he thinks it's awesome.
你告诉妈妈  她会兴奋地跟你击掌
Heck, you tell your mom, she high-fives you so fast,
甚至连烤箱手套都来不及摘
she doesn't even take off her oven mitts.
个中滋味若有人懂
But if they had any idea how difficult it is:
醋海里翻波  不安里浮沉
the jealousy, the insecurity,
连击掌都变成慰问击掌
those high-fives would be high-fives of condolence.
巴尼  根本没有所谓的慰问击掌
Barney, condolence high-fives are not a thing.
当然有
They're a thing.
当天早些时候...
不好意思  我们不得不辞退你
I'm afraid we're gonna have to let you go.
来  击掌
Up top.
别光听我说我这些无聊的情侣问题了
Ah, listen to me and my boring couples' problems.
你怎么样
How are you?
单身生活过得好吗
How's the single life?
没什么感觉  自从罗宾这事后
I wouldn't know. After this whole Robin thing,
目前的我  比较低调
for the time being, I'm laying low.
你是说...
Laying low as in
标准低到跟很矮的妞上床吗
sleeping with a really short chick?
你们有玩39式吗
You guys doing 39?
我是说我没出去约会
I mean, I'm not seeing anyone.
我要努力忘记罗宾
I'm just, you know, trying to get Robin out of my head.
你该"换换口味"
You need a palate cleanser.
巴尼  求你了  千万别撮合
Barney, please, don't try to set me up
我和昆茵的脱衣舞女同事
with Quinn's stripper friends.
我才不会呢
Oh, I wouldn't dream of it.
为什么不  我暗示得还不够多吗
Why not, how many hints do I have to drop?!
不是  我想的是比较传统的方式
No, I'm thinking of something much more traditional.
-如网络交友  -不用了  谢谢
- Online dating. - Yeah, no thanks.
拜托  泰德  都2012了
Come on, Ted! It's 2012.
你还指望在书店看报纸的时候
What do you expect, to meet some cute travel agent
邂逅漂亮的旅游中介吗
when you're reading a newspaper at a bookstore?
现在没这种事了
None of those things exist anymore.
巴尼  我是绝对不可能
Barney, I will never, ever, ever,
去尝试网络交友的
try online dating.
那天晚上我试了网络交友
That night I tried online dating.
孩子们  我遇到的第一个女孩就很棒
And kids, the first girl I found was amazing:
她漂亮聪明  风趣幽默
beautiful, smart, funny,
热爱战前建筑
huge fan of prewar architecture,
最喜欢的诗人是聂鲁达
favorite poet Neruda,
聂鲁达  智利当代著名诗人
最喜欢的电影是《捉鬼敢死队》
favorite movie Ghostbusters,
而且不讨厌克利夫兰
and she didn't hate Cleveland.
她简直太完美了
She's perfect.
于是我给她发了封邮件
So I sent her an email,
邀请她去打迷你高尔夫
inviting her to mini golf.
-喂  -迷你高尔夫
- Hello. - Mini golf?
谁第一次约会去打迷你高尔夫啊
Who takes a first date to mini golf?
我现在过去
I'm coming over!
泰德  泰德  泰迪小德德
Oh, Ted-Ted-Ted- Teddy-Ted-Ted.
谁让你进来的
Who buzzed you in?
你真以为你玩网络交友时
Did you really think you could start dating online,
我会不知道吗
and I wouldn't find out?
可这个女孩  她是...
But with thi-this girl, sh-she was...
我  她就是我  泰德
Me. She was me, Ted.
照片就是随便找了个你没见过的
The photo was just of some girl I knew you'd never seen before,
娱乐体育电视网的知名体育主播
a very famous sports anchor on ESPN.
巴尼  我不用你在网上帮我找女人
Barney, I don't need you to help me find a girl online.
当然  因为我已经找完了
Exactly because I've already done it!
而且是3个
Three girls in fact.
我地毯式搜索了所有交友网站
I scoured the dating sites
用了自己写的对数函数
using my own personal logarithms,
考虑了各种变量因素
factoring in a broad spectrum of variables,
过滤掉不合标准的高风险对象
filtering out undesirable high-risk negatives,
同时保证83%的成功率...
guaranteeing a success rate of 83...
谁的胸部露得最多  你就选谁
You picked the girls that showed the most boob.
我的方法可是百试百灵
My methods get results.
你跟这3个妞出去约会
Go out with these three girls,
我保证你的口味焕然一新
and your palate is going to be so cleansed,
崭新锃亮到能看见自己的倒影
you will see your reflection in it.
到时候
And when you do,
好好打理下你的头发
you can fix the hair,
因为...你最近有照过镜子吗
because... Have you seen yourself?
没有  不过我最近倒是见过
No, but you know what I have seen,
你脱衣舞女女友的咪咪哟
your stripper girlfriend's cans.
这玩笑开得有点过了  对吧
That was going way too far, wasn't it?
对不起
I'm sorry.
来个慰问击掌吧
My condolences.
靠  马修因为宝宝的到来神经紧张
Man, Marshall's really stressing out about this baby.
他读各种孕妇书
He's reading every book,
看哺乳记录片
watching breast-feeding documentaries.
某天早上我醒来  他把我裹的像个婴儿
I woke up the other day, he had swaddled me.
虽然那确实是几个月来  我睡的最香的一觉
Sure, it was the best night's sleep I had had in months,
但还是...
but still...
你知道他现在又搞什么吗
You know what his latest thing is?
什么鬼东西在响
What the hell is that?
马修  你搞什么啊
Marshall, what is that?
我定了闹铃  每3小时响一次
I rigged this alarm to go off every three hours.
我要把生物钟调整到
I'm training myself for the
新生儿父母的不规则睡觉模式
sporadic sleep patterns of early parenthood.
你不介意的话
Now, if you'll excuse me,
我要哄我的演练宝宝睡觉了
I have a practice-baby to soothe.
你得跟他谈谈
You got to talk to him.
好吧  我晚上跟他说
Yeah, I'll talk to him tonight.
还是明早再说吧
Maybe tomorrow morning.
-还想再被裹一晚吗  -真的睡得好香
- One last swaddle? - It's just so cozy.
感觉像睡在热乎乎的墨西哥卷饼里
It's like sleeping in a warm burrito.
与此同时  巴尼准备面对
Meanwhile, Barney was about to have
脱衣舞女男友的最糟的噩梦
a stripper's boyfriend's worst nightmare.
卡玛
Karma?
天啊  你的腿没绕到脖子后面
Oh, my gosh, I didn't recognize you
我都没认出来是你
without your legs behind your head.
达瑞尔  你没穿那件难看的风衣
Darryl, I didn't recognize you
我也没认出来是你
without your creepy trench coat.
你怎么样
How are you?
-挺好的  你明天上班吗  -你知道的
- Great, you working tomorrow? - You know it.
那就好  明天我一定穿戴好装备去
Great. I'll be there with bells on.
装备就是超薄运动裤
And by bells, I mean super thin sweatpants.
真恶心
Gross.
他这个人其实挺好的
He's actually a nice guy.
虽然当副市长很忙
he's so busy as deputy mayor,
但总记得在我生日送卡片
but I always get a card on my birthday.
昆茵  我爱你是个脱衣舞女
Quinn, I love the fact that you're a stripper,
但同时  我又很你是个脱衣舞女
but I hate the fact that you're a stripper.
巴尼  我喜欢我的工作
Barney, I like my job.
我不需要被谁拯救
And I do not need to be rescued.
所以  别当我的英雄
So, don't be that guy.
你说得对  你说得对
You're right, you're right.
我明白  当我没说过
I got it. Forget I said anything.
晚上去捧你的场  卡玛
I'll see you tonight, Karma.
没问题  淫贱拉里
You got it, Dirty Larry.
你必须辞了这个工作
You have to quit your job!
那晚  我和巴尼挑的第一个女孩约会
That night, I went out with the first girl Barnrn picked for me.
只是有个问题
There was just one problem.
你叫罗宾
Your name is Robin?
对  后鼻音
Yeah, with a Y.
是朗宾啊
Oh, Yobin.
不  是罗冰
No, Robyn.
我的网上资料写着"威士忌与枪支"
I go by scotch and gun lover in my online profile,
那是因为我最喜欢这两样东西
'cause those are my two favorite things.
还有就是加拿大  我的家乡和祖国
Well, next to Canada, my home and native land.
加拿大
Oh. Canada.
就这样
And just like that,
罗冰成了罗宾
Robyn became Robin.
近来好吗  泰德
How's it going, Ted?
太好了
Oh, good.
瞧  你老妈舍得从酒吧回来了
Hey, look, mommy's back from the bar!
老爸终于可以去洗澡了
Now I can finally take a shower.
这尿布真臭
This diaper smells.
别告诉我怎么弄的
I don't want to know.
好了  马修
Okay, Marshall,
快坐下  我们得谈谈
sit down; we need to talk.
听着  我知道你也是一片好心
Look, I know you mean well,
可我们离预产期还有五周
but we have five weeks till the due date.
我们不能利用这段时间放松下吗
Can't we use this time to just relax?
等宝宝出生后
We'll figure out how all this stuff
这些事情自然就懂了嘛
works after the baby comes.
等宝宝出生后
After the baby comes?
对  我们可以边做边学
Yeah, we'll learn on the job.
边做边...真逗
Learn on the j... Huh.
莉莉
Wow, you know, Lily,
或许现在的燃眉之急
maybe the crisis here
不是我没准备好当爹
isn't that I'm not ready to be a dad;
而是你没准备好当妈
maybe it's that you're not ready to be a mom!
-你说什么  -对
- Excuse me?! - Yeah.
就这样  他俩吵了起来
With that, an argument began,
个中细节至今仍存在很大的争议
the details of which are still hotly debated to this day.
比如说  马修叔叔发誓说绝没说过这句
For instance, Uncle Marshall swears he never said:
-我是唯一为这孩子做出牺牲的人  -什么
- I'm the only one making sacrifices for this baby! - What?!
同时他也声称自己所说  句句属实
And he claims he never actually altered the words:
你就像连自己怀孕了都不知道一样
It's like you don't even know that you're pregnant!
同时  莉莉坚称这一段被夸大其词
While Lily insists this part was exaggerated:
宝宝很好弄
Baby's are easy;
只要看着他们卖萌  然后喂意大利面就好了
you just watch them be cute and feed them spaghetti!
不过大家都对收场意见一致
But everyone agrees this is how the argument ended:
马修  我要的不过是一点点清静
Marshall, what I need now is some peace, some quiet,
不过现在我要的是  吃点意大利面
and now that it's out there, some spaghetti.
帮忙拉我起来  好让我夺门而出
Now, please help me off the couch so I can storm out.
第二天  我告诉巴尼我的约会经过
The next day, I filled Barney in on my date.
朗宾
Oh, Yobin.
不  是罗冰
No, Robyn.
而之后的整晚
And for the rest of the night,
只要我一看她  就会想到罗宾
every time I looked at her, I just saw Robin's face.
-那是应该的啊  -不  是我们的罗宾
- Well, I should hope so. - No, our Robin.
有个I[眼睛]
Robin with an I.
I和eye[眼睛]同音
我们的罗宾有两只眼睛  朋友
Uh, our Robin has two eyes, my friend.
不过也不错  你已经开始忘记她的长相了
But that's good. You're forgetting what she looks like.
我理解  这过程一定很艰难
I'm sorry, that must have been tough.
如果有人能感同身受  那一定是我
If anyone knows what that feels like, it's me.
请接受我的慰问
My condolence.
好了  向前看吧
Okay. Moving on.
下一个女孩  味道大不同
The next girl: perfect palate cleanser.
和罗宾完全不同
Nothing like Robin.
怎么个不同
How nothing?
我放眼望向世界
I gaze out into the world and all I see
只看到葬送梦想的冰冷之地
is an icy place where dreams die.
哇  千层面
Ooh, lasagna.
近来好吗  泰德
How's it going, Ted?
什么  不  怎么会这样
What? No. What? Wh-Why?
记得吗  我有次做了千层面
Remember, I made lasagna that one time.
这样你就来啦
That's all it takes?
那都算不上千层面  你是往做坏的犹太面上
It wasn't even lasagna; you took your botched kugle
倒了番茄酱
and poured tomato sauce on it.
我可没说那千层面做得好
I didn't say it was good lasagna.
对了  你没事干嘛勾搭这种女的呢
By the way, what are you doing with this girl?
手臂上满是纹身  而且...
With tattoos all up and down her arms and...
其他地方也不放过
everywhere else.
瞧啊  我的妈呀
Hello... good gravy.
那条龙尾巴是不是一直延伸到她的...
Does that dragons tail go all the way down to her...
没错  我猜对了
Ohh, yes, it does.
你还想我怎么样  罗宾
Well, what do you want me to do, Robin?
我总得设法忘掉你
I have to get over you somehow,
而且如果非得这样...
and if this is what it takes...
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
你有点魂不守舍
You kind of spaced out there.
怪胎
Weirdo.
"所以  总的来说
"So, in summation,
我非常非常抱歉"
I'm very, very sorry."
"我猜我只是太想独占你
"I guess I just wanted you all to myself,
而我想到这些怪人打量你的..."
and then I thought of all the creepy guys groping at your..."
"好吧  我又要生气了
"Okay, I'm getting mad again,
所以我在此搁笔了"
so I'm going to stop writing now."
"请享用这些巧克力  可能含花生[鸡鸡]哟"
"Please enjoy these chocolates, may contain peanuts."
peanuts与penis谐音
亲一个就和好吧
Kiss and make up?
在窗前打一炮就和好吧
Have sex up against the window and make up?
你这里风景还真不错
You do have a great view.
你这么说还真有意思
Well, funny you should mention that.
因为这是你的风景
It's your view.
兄台  再说一次
Come again for Big Fudge?
恭喜你  你被录用了
Congratulations. You're hired.
你是巨人国家银行
You are Goliath National Bank's
新任执行战略协调员
newest executive strategy coordinator.
执行战略协调员是什么啊
What is an executive strategy coordinator?
是几个感觉跟企业有关的词
It's three corporate-sounding words
合起来造就的一个假职位
which, when added together, equal a fake job
但你可以得到一份实打实的薪水
for which you get a real paycheck
和你做脱衣舞娘赚的钱一样多呢
in the amount of exactly what you'd make stripping.
还有牙科保险  不客气
Plus dental. You're welcs.
现在该靠窗打炮了...
Now, about that up-against-the-window sex...
兄台  我不想在银行工作
Dude, I don't want to work for a bank.
为什么
Why not?
因为我不是无下限的
Because I have standards.
你们这些人就是妓女
You people are whores.
为了钱  任人摆布
The things you're willing to do just for some money,
不知廉耻
it's shameful.
你可是在脱衣舞厅工作呢
You work in a strip club.
对  我喜欢我的工作
Yeah, and I like it.
而且我是行内高手
And I'm good at it.
巴尼
Barney,
如果我接受这份工作  那我就成了你的人
if I took this job, you would own me.
我将得乖乖步入牢笼
I would be willingly stepping into a cage,
这不是我想要的生活
which is something I don't do.
除了周四
Except on Thursdays,
"情欲小野猫"的牢笼夜
when it's cage night at the Lusty Leopard,
可那是个纸板箱牢笼
but that's a cardboard cage,
我随时都可以出笼
and I can get out of it any time I want.
是吗
You can?
牢笼夜的惊险都被你拆穿了
Wow, thanks for ruining cage night.
-别这样  昆茵  -不
- Come on, Quinn. - No.
-我不会...  -不
- I wouldn't... - Nope.
别说了
Don't.
我想要回去好好想想
I think I have some thinking to do.
我...
I...
斯丁森先生
Mr. Stinson?
现在我是不是不用离职了
Does this mean I get to keep my job?
对  赫姆  你可以留下
Yeah, Herm, you can stay.
宝贝  听着
Hey, baby, listen.
我很抱歉  我刚才太激动了
I'm-I'm sorry I flipped out.
没关系
Oh, that's okay.
说实在的  或许错在我
To be fair, maybe I'm at fault
太爱我们的孩子了
for loving our child too much,
尽管这就是为人父母的定义  所以...
although that is the definition of parenting, so...
好吧  算和好了吧
All right, good make up.
听着  我刚才上网
Hey, listen, I went online,
发现了一个"宝宝训练营"
and I found this Baby Boot Camp thing
这周末会在帕拉默斯的一家酒店举办培训
that they're doing at a hotel in Paramus this weekend.
"宝宝训练营"
Baby Boot Camp?
听起来不错
That sounds great.
是啊  这是个两天的项目
Yeah, it's a two-day event...
我们要去
We're going.
...还有很多研讨会和课程
...and there's lots of seminars and classes.
咱们一定要参加
You've already made the sale.
我已经给我们俩报了名
Anyway, I signed us up.
完全听不进去  我的心已经开始打包行李了
Not even listening anymore; mentally packing.
我在想绕过收费口去帕拉默斯的
I'm trying to figure out the best way to get to Paramus
最佳路线
without hitting any tolls.
这训练营一定很棒
This is gonna be great.
那就是我最后一次
And that was the last time
和留胡子的人约会
I'll ever go out with a guy with a mustache.
这次不错
This is good.
不错  我没在想那个谁
This is nice, not thinking about you-know-who.
只陶醉其中
Just having a good time
感谢上帝  我没留胡子
and thanking God I didn't grow that mustache.
而你
And you,
你真有礼貌
you're so polite.
我的前未婚夫  韦恩  他一点礼貌都没
My ex-fiancé, Wayne, he had no manners.
韦恩没礼貌
Wayne had no manners.
韦恩...礼貌...
Wayne... manners...
韦恩庄园  布鲁斯·韦恩的家
Wayne Manor, home of Bruce Wayne,
他以饰演蜘蛛侠而闻名
better known as Batman,
迪克·格雷森的导师  韦恩的养子迪克
mentor to Dick Grayson, his orphan ward
在夜晚会在穿上"神奇小子"彩色制服
who at night would don the colorful vestments
人们又叫他为
of the Boy Wonder, aka...
"罗宾"
Robin.
你喝一口饮料能编这么多啊  泰德
Holy long walk for a short drink of water, Ted.
闭嘴
Stop this.
我要你离开我的世界
I need you out of my life for real.
-你才不要呢  -我就要
- You don't mean that. - Yes, I do.
不  你不要
No, you don't.
泰德  今非昔比啊
Look how much is changing right now.
马修和莉莉快生孩子了
Marshall and Lily are having a baby.
巴尼和一个女人同居了
Barney's shacking up with a girl.
你的整个世界  发生了翻天覆地的变化
With your whole world turning upside down,
你难道不想死死守住
isn't a friendship like this one
我们这样的一段友谊吗
something you want to hold on to as tightly as possible?
每看你一眼  我的心就多痛一分
And every time I look at you, it hurts.
这就是我唯一一次的当拉拉的经历
...and that's the story of my only lesbian experience.
抱歉  细节部分说太多了
I'm sorry for going into so much detail.
我以后再也不讲这事了
I'll never tell that story again.
对了  饭菜还合胃口吗
Anyway, how's your meal?
霍莉  听我说  或许我该坦白
Holly, listen, I should probably tell you,
其实  我对某人仍余情未了
um, I'm kind of getting over someone right now.
很高兴听到你这么说
I am so glad you said that.
我对韦恩也还念念不忘
I guess I'm still getting over Wayne.
要走出一段感情实在太难
It's been really hard.
两位要来份果汁冰糕吗
Can I interest you in some sorbet?
你俩看起来都该"换换口味"了
You two look like you could both use a palate cleanser.
我这顿饭菜合你胃口吗  泰德
How's your palate, Ted?
焕然一新
Pretty cleansed.
在研讨会上
You know, at this seminar,
将会有某位自许"育儿专家"的人
there's gonna be the one guy who's, like, Mr. Parenting Expert,
时不时用自己的"重要观点"  打断讲师的话
keeps interrupting the speakers with his own "important facts."
而那个人  就坐在你旁边
And you're gonna be sitting right next to him,
准备大开眼界吧
so get ready for that.
亲爱的  你最近有点睡眠不足
Baby, you've been a little sleep deprived lately.
不如让我开车吧
Why don't you let me drive?
这个主意倒是不坏
You know what, that's not such a bad idea.
可我们都不希望看到
I mean, the last thing we want is
我一坐上驾驶座就...
for me to get behind the wheel and just...
亲爱的  你可真香
Oh, baby, you smell good.
等我们到了酒店
When we get to that hotel,
我要与你颠鸾倒凤  缠绵不休
I'm gonna wear your pregnant belly like a hat.
那你可得先把我灌醉哟
You'll have to buy me a couple of cocktails first.
巴  巴尼
Bar-Barney!
我们这是在哪儿
Where are we?
大西洋城啊  宝贝
Atlantic City, baby!
其实还有14英里才到
Well, in 14 miles.
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
莉莉人呢
And where is Lily?
你对我的"演练宝宝"做了什么
And what did you do to the practice baby?
宝宝还有剩吗
And is there any left?
莉莉很担心你
Lily was worried about you.
她认为你该放松一下  所以...
She thought you needed to unwind, so...
我们都不希望看到
I mean, the last thing we want is for me to
我一坐上驾驶座就...
get behind the wheel and just...
她在棕榈泉订了两间豪华套房
She made reservations for two deluxe rooms,
按摩  还有晚餐
massages, and dinner at the Palm,
作为交换  我烤了饼干给她
and in return, I made her cookies.
所以华尔道夫酒店的宝宝预热营是假的咯
So, there's no Baby Boot Camp at the Paramus Waldorf?
话说帕拉默斯有华尔道夫酒店吗
Is there even a Paramus Waldorf?
老弟
Bro...
莉莉这是要气死我呀
I am so mad at Lily right now.
她早料到你会这样
She knew you would be;
所以她准备了这个
that's why she packed this.
我的"气死莉莉"T恤
My Mad-at-Lily shirt.
这是我为我的
I had this made for me
高中女友史戴芙专门订做的衣服
and my high school girlfriend, Steph.
实际上  "马修和史戴芙  天长地久"
In reality, "Marshall and Steph 4-eva"
结果却成了
turned out to be
"马修和史戴芙  两天分手
"Marshall and Steph for two days
因为史戴芙的男友提前一周出了少管所"
until Steph's boyfriend got out of juvie a week early."
每次穿这个  莉莉都气得要死
Drives Lily crazy when I wear it.
希望没了我  她孤苦凄惨
I hope she's miserable without me.
泰德  最近如何啊
Hey, Ted, how's tricks?
相当不错  卢
Tricks are pretty good, Lou.
前几天遇到了点感情上的麻烦  不过
Had some girl trouble earlier in the week, but, uh,
我感觉从今往后  事情会越来越...
I got a feeling from here on out, things are gonna be A...
靠  你有完没完啊
O-Oh, you son of a bitch.
你好呀
Hello.
莉莉说得对
Lily's right.
我最近太不正常了
I've been acting crazy.
没关系  老弟
No, it's okay, bro.
我是说  你最近是有点不正常
I mean, yeah, you've been a little crazy,
可那都是因为爱
but it comes from love.
这种不正常  就和某男愿意
It's the same kind of crazy that makes a man
从政府援助金里拿出50万大洋
offer his stripper girlfriend over half a million dollars
付给他的脱衣舞娘女友
of government bailout money,
只要她别在男人的老二上蹭来蹭去一样
not to rub up on other guys' junk.
我们都是出于善意
It's good crazy.
希望莉莉没事
I hope Lily's okay.
够了  老弟
Okay, you know, that's it, bro.
我们俩都关掉手机一小时
We're both turning off our phones for one hour.
动议被否决
Motion denied.
好吧  你让我别无选择
Okay, you leave me no choice.
我提议  我们关机1小时享受兄弟时间
Proposal: you give me one hour of phone-free bro time,
在此期间我们  也就是你自己
during which we, and by we I mean you,
来个前无古人  后无来者的酩酊大醉
get magnificently, mythologically drunk.
我是指"醉得说话都得带字幕"的那种
I'm talking needing-subtitles- when-you-speak drunk.
如果你能做到
If you can give me that,
我就系上这个
I will wear this.
小鸭领带
The ducky tie?
我以为你早把它扔了呢
I thought you threw that thing away.
我是扔了
I did.
它自己回来了
It came back.
好吧  巴尼
All right, Barney,
你成功打动我了
you got yourself a deal.
不好意思  小姐
Um, excuse me, miss.
你有空的话
Um, when you get a chance,
能请你端来100杯龙舌兰酒吗
could you bring over a hundred shots of tequila, please?
也给我来一份
I'll have the same.
你为什么就不能放过我呢
Why are you still here?
你觉得呢
Why do you think I'm still here?
我猜是因为我还爱着你吧
I guess because I'm in love with you.
不然怎么会走到哪里  都能看到你的脸
Why else would I be seeing your face everywhere I look?
那是因为你心里难过
Because you feel bad.
我当然难过
Of course I feel bad.
我告诉你  我爱你
I told you I love you,
而显然
which is apparently
这是最不应该说出口的一句话
the worst thing you can say to someone.
这不是你难过的原因
That's not why you feel bad.
你难过是因为  你说了这句话
You feel bad because after you said it,
却还是放手让我走掉
you let me go away.
我明白我们的关系
I know our relationship
和你期望的不太一样
isn't exactly what you want it to be,
我也知道  或许我不如你爱我那般深
and I know I may not love you the way you love me,
但  我是爱你的
but I do love you.
这难道不值得死死守住吗
Isn't that worth hanging on to?
我好想你
I miss you.
金温尿牌啤酒[马修前下属生产的啤酒  参见S6E07]
还不快去把我找回来
So go get me back.
罗宾
Robin?
泰德
Ted.
能见到你真人太好了
It's good to really see you.
我是说  能见到你真太好了
I mean, it's really good to see you.
我们应该好好谈谈
Look, I think we need to talk.
我也这么想  可现在不是时候
Uh, me, too, but now's not a good time.
为什么
Why not?
为你骄傲  老弟
I am proud of you, bro.
你不但关机1小时
You turned off your phone for one hour,
还喝得酩酊大醉
and you got so drunk...
现在我说话都得挂上字幕
要的就是这效果
Exactly.
我说  巴尼
干嘛  马修
Yes, Marshall?
咱现在能把手机打开了不
当然可以
Well, I don't see why not.
哎哟  我有17条语音留言呢
Whoa! I've got 17 new voicemails.
巴尼  我是莉莉
Barney, it's Lily.
你俩最好赶紧滚回纽约
You guys need to get back to New York right away.
我快生了
I'm in labor.
向啤酒猛男里斯致敬
All hail Beercules!
马修喝醉后给自己取的外号  参见S7E2
万岁
Yeah!
好吧  巴尼  你成功打动我了
All right, Barney, you got yourself a deal.
这是马修的语音信箱
Hey, you've reached Marshall.
请留言
Please leave a message.
亲爱的  是我
Hey, baby, it's me.
我可能快生了
I think I'm labor.
我们应该每周来一次
We should do this every weekend.
这次是真的
Okay, this is real.
不是在玩狼来了
It's not a false alarm.
我真的要生了
This is real; I'm in labor.
我要你赶快回我电话
I kind of need you to call me back now.
你说你如此娇小
How does somebody so little
手指怎么会如此有力呢
have such strong fingers?
你在哪里
Where are you?
回我电话
Call me!
这位兄弟是帕拉默斯的华尔道夫酒店经理
He is the manager of the Paramus Waldorf.
你要是来帕拉默斯玩  我们罩着你
You come to Paramus, we will hook you up.
如果你是想要借机报复我
If you're trying to get back at me,
那你这招可真是他妈的大错特错了
you have chosen a wildly inappropriate way of doing so!
爽哉  美哉
Oh, yeah... Oh, yeah.